RESUME



EDUCATION

JUN 2013 - MAR 2014

10th Boards

R.S.M. Poonawala Sarvajanik Experimental School, Surat

JUN 2015 - MAR 2016

12th Boards

R.S.M. Poonawala Sarvajanik Experimental School. Surat

AUG 2016 - PRESENT

B.E in Computer Engineering

R.N.G. Patel Institute of Technology, Bardoli

SKILLS

C/C++

JAVA

Kotlin

PHP

JavaScript

HTML / CSS

KULDIP PATEL

Phone: +91 9998897742 | **Email:** patel.kuldip91@gmail.com

Address: 33-1/109, Near Ambika Niketan Temple, Parle Point, Surat, Gujarat 395007

ABOUT ME

I'm 21 years old Intermediate Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the Android apps and Websites. Skilled in C++, Java, PHP, Android and Cyber Security. Currently Studying in Computer Science and Engineering in R.N.G. Patel Institute of Technology, Bardoli, Gujarat.

EXPERIENCE

SEP 2019

Lead Backend Developer | Visvesmruti 2019

RNGPIT - Gujarat - India

MAR 2019 - OCT 2019

Student Partner | Internshala

RNGPIT - Gujarat - India

JAN 2019 - PRESENT

Developer Student Club Community Lead | DSC RNGPIT

RNGPIT - Gujarat - India

WEBSITES AND PROFILES

Website: kuldippatel.dev

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/kp7742 **GitHub:** github.com/kp7742 **Twitter:** twitter.com/BinXploit